Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1948-1983, undated (bulk 1959-1979) MS 3009-RG 6.I MS 3009-RG 6TEST
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Editor-in-Chief: Subseries I.B. Henry Anatole Grunwald Files, 1944-1998 (bulk 1968-1987); 74.0 Linear feet; (74 boxes)
  - Subsubseries I.B.3. Departmental Files, 1946-1987; 25.0 Linear feet; (25 boxes)
    - 1974: Report of the European Task Force (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 1)
    - 1974: Coffey Surveys of the News (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 2)
    - 1974: Nixon Editorial Ideas (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 3)
    - 1974: Puerto Rico Time Marketing, September 8-12, 1974, [Meeting] Notes (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 4)
    - 1974: Bilderberg, April 18-21, 1974 [Meeting Notes] (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 5)
    - 1974: Comparison of White House Passages (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 6)
      The passages are from transcripts of Nixon conversations.
    - 1974: Yankelovich (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 7)
    - 1974: The Trilateral Commission (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 8)
    - 1974: Man of the Year (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 9)
    - 1974: Energy Conference, April 28 to May 1, 1974 (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 10)
    - 1974: Time Inc. Archives (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 11)
    - 1974: Bernie Auer (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 12)
    - 1974: Charley Bear (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 13)
    - 1974: William Bishop (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 14)
    - 1974: Books and Arts Associates Budget (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 15)
    - 1974: Budget Schedule (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 16)
    - 1974: Conflict of Interest (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 17)
    - 1974: Corporate Contributions and Memberships (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 18)
    - 1974: Corporate Circulation Budget (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 19)
    - 1974: Corporate Management Committee (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 20)
    - 1974: Editorial Services Budget (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 21)
    - 1974: Fuerbringer, Otto (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 22)
    - 1974: Fortune Budget Notes (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 23)
    - 1974: Harry Johnston (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 24)
    - 1974: Jeanne Kerr (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 25)
    - 1974: Art Keylor (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 26)
    - 1974: Jerry Korn (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 27)
    - 1974: James Linen (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 28)
    - 1974: Lunches (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 29)
    - 1974: Mail Order Sales (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 30)
    - 1974: Managing Editors Lunch (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 31)
    - 1974: Carolyn McCandless (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 32)
    - 1974: Money (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 33)
    - 1974: National Magazine Awards [empty] (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 34)
    - 1974: Net Paid Circulation: All Magazines (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 35)
    - 1974: People, Money, and Magazine Development Budgets (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 36)
    - 1974: Gabe Perle [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1974: Pioneer Press Budget (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 37)
    - 1974: Printing Developments Division Balance Sheets (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 38)
    - 1974: Real Estate Division Budget (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 39)
    - 1974: Sports Illustrated Budget (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 40)
    - 1974: Subscription Service Division Budget (Offsite-box 1023, Folder 41)
    - 1974: Time Inc. Budget (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 1)
    - 1974: Time-Life Films Budget (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 2)
    - 1974: Don Wilson (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 3)
    - 1974: Writers and Researchers: Complaints (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 4)
    - 1974: New Work Week: Monday-Friday (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 5)
    - 1974: Washington Bureau (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 6)
    - 1975: 5/75 Trip: Requiem in Leningrad (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 7)
    - 1975: Future of Magazines (Gart Memo to Keylor) (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 8)
    - 1975: November Trip Notes (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 9)
    - 1975: Man of the Year (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 10)
    - 1975: Newspaper Articles (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 11)
    - 1975: Money Speech (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 12)
    - 1975: Bicentennial Memos (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 13-15)
    - 1975: Bicentennial Essays (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 16)
    - 1975: Nixon Tapes (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 17)
    - 1975: Leadership Candidate (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 18)
    - 1975: Canada (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 19)
    - 1975: Time Study (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 20)
    - 1975: Staff Committee (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 21)
    - 1976: Reorganization (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 22-23)
    - 1976: Strike Post-Mortem Memo to Donovan (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 24)
    - 1976: Campaign Coverage (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 25)
    - 1976: Time and Newsweek Analysis (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 26)
    - 1976: Giscard Letter and Others (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 27)
    - 1976: Expense Reports (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 28)
    - 1976: Strike Memos (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 29)
    - 1976: Descendants of Signers (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 30)
    - 1976: New York Conference on Media and the Law (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 31)
    - 1976: Time Editorial Expense History (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 32)
    - 1976: Thank-you Notes for Help During Strike (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 33)
    - 1976: Sloan Foundation: Fellows in Economics Journalism (Offsite-box 1024, Folder 34)
    - 1976: Sloan Foundation: Notes from the Managing Editor (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 1)
    - 1976: Leadership (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 2-3)
    - 1976: Southern Issue (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 4)
    - 1976: Leadership Project (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 5-6)
    - 1976: Time/Leadership Conference (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 7-8)
    - 1976: Time/Leadership Conference: Binder Cover (Offsite-box 1056, Folder 1)
    - 1977: Legal Department (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 9)
    - 1977: Legal Department [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1977: Letters of Congratulations [Editorial Director] (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 10-11)
    - 1977: Personal (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 12)
    - 1977: Transition (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 13)
    - 1977: Kissinger Party (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 14)
    - 1977: Interviews for South Africa Essay (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 15-16)
    - 1977: Africa Trip: May (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 17)
    - 1977: Kenya (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 18)
    - 1977: South Africa (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 19)
    - 1977: Rhodesia (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 20)
    - 1977: Interview by Japanese: October (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 21)
    - 1977: Time/Update on America '77: Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 22-23)
    - 1977: Time Distribution Services Meeting: Houston (Offsite-box 1025, Folder 24)
    - 1977: Louis Banks Report [on Time Inc. editorial departments] (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 1)
    - 1977: Nadasdy Memo on Begin Cover (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 2)
    - 1977: Time Statistics (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 3)
    - 1977: Roger Kahn-Lois Wallace Letter of Agreement (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 4)
    - 1977: Roger Kahn-Lois Wallace Letter of Agreement [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1977: Jefferson Portrait Presentation [to the University of Virginia] (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 5)
    - 1977: New York World Times: The Daily Newssummary Prospectus (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 6)
    - 1977: Media and Business Seminar: Princeton (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 7)
    - 1977: Time/Update on America '77 (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 8)
    - 1977: Time/Update on America '77 (Offsite-box 1056, Folder 3)
    - 1977: Energy Conference (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 9)
    - 1977: Energy Conference: Binder Cover (Offsite-box 1056, Folder 2)
    - 1978: December Lunch with Donovan (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 10)
      Contains Grunwald's account of being asked to serve as Editor-in-Chief.
    - 1978: Transition: Announcement (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 11)
    - 1978: 20th Century Fund Task Force: International Flow of News and London Trip (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 12-13)
    - 1978: Arms Roundtable (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 14)
    - 1978: George Kennan (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 15)
    - 1978: 20th Century Fund Dinner (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 16)
    - 1978: Carter Essay (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 17)
    - 1978: Time Covers: National Gallery (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 18)
    - 1978: Time Covers: National Gallery [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
      The restricted file contains the gift agreement transferring Time Inc.'s collection of Time covers to the National Gallery of Art.
    - 1978: White House Dinner (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 19)
    - 1978: Heiskell's Dinner for Caramanlis (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 20)
    - 1978: Creative Conference: Cambridge (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 21)
    - 1978: Stanford Supreme Court Decision: Alicia Patterson meeting (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 22)
    - 1978: Research for Tax Conference (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 23)
    - 1978: Tax Roundtable: Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box 1026, Folder 24-25)
    - 1978: North Carolina Seminar (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 1-2)
    - 1978: Tirman's Report on Barraclough (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 3)
    - 1978: Katharine Graham: Washington Star Series (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 4)
    - 1978: Friendship (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 5)
    - 1978: Legal (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 6)
    - 1978: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1978: Background History on Irredentist Examples (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 7)
    - 1978: Grunwald/Ferenbaugh Piece: Irredentism (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 8)
    - 1978: Time Style (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 9)
    - 1978: "Who's on Time?" Covers (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 10)
    - 1978: Time Covers: Cover Art (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 11)
    - 1978: Time Covers: Subject Matter: 1958-1977 (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 12)
    - 1978: World Press Freedom Committee (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 13-15)
    - 1978: 20th Century Fund and Blenheim Meeting (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 16-17)
    - 1978: Woman: Outside Consultants (Offsite-box 1027, Folder 18-19)
    - 1978: Woman: Consultants (Offsite-box 1027-1028)
    - 1978: Woman: Reactions (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 2-3)
    - 1978: Critiques of 2nd Woman Dummy [empty] (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 4)
    - 1978: Time Inc. Conference on Taxation (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 5-6)
    - 1978: A PLO State: Mortal Danger (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 7)
    - 1979: Time Inc. Conference on Anti-Trust (contents removed to 1979 Public Affairs) (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 8)
    - 1979: Magazine Development (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 9-11)
    - 1979: Kissinger Memoirs (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 12)
    - 1979: Kissinger Memoirs [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1979: The Family: Ken Pierce (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 13)
    - 1979: Second Science Dummy (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 14-15)
      Regarding beginning of Discover including the prospectus.
    - 1979: Science Magazine: Jaroff (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 16-17)
    - 1979: Life vs. Look (Offsite-box 1028, Folder 18)
    - 1979: Notes of Congratulations [for Editor-in-Chief appointment]: A-L (Offsite-box 1028-1029)
    - 1979: Notes of Congratulations [for Editor-in-Chief appointment]: M-Z (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 3-5)
    - 1979: The Role of Editor-in-Chief (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 6)
    - 1979: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 7)
    - 1979: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1979: Memos to All Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 8)
    - 1979: Mondale Visit (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 9)
    - 1979: Fortune Notes (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 10)
    - 1979: Ford Memoirs: Nation Article (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 11)
    - 1979: Ford Memoirs: Nation Article [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1979: Salt II Symposium (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 12)
    - 1979: Washington Star (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 13)
    - 1979: The 80s Issue (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 14)
    - 1979: World Press Freedom Committee (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 15-17)
    - 1979: Time Anti-Trust Conference (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 18)
    - 1979: Donovan Dinner (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 19)
    - 1979: "50 Faces for the Future" (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 20)
    - 1979: Washington Star Party (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 21)
    - 1979: Chicago-Des Moines (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 22)
    - 1979: Ted Kennedy Dinner (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 23)
    - 1979: Fidel Castro Dinner (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 24)
    - 1979: Notes on Cuba Trip (Offsite-box 1029, Folder 25)
    - 1980: World Press Freedom Committee and Muskie Meeting in Washington (Offsite-box 1029-1030)
    - 1980: Legal (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 2)
      Includes trademark use policy.
    - 1980: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1980: Assorted Memos (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 3)
    - 1980: Memos to all Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 4)
    - 1980: Duncan's Washington Meeting (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 5)
      1 audiocassette: analog,; 1 15/16 x 1 5/16 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "Lucey." On side B label: "Yankelovich."
      1 audiocassette: analog,; 1 15/16 x 1 5/16 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "Strauss." On side B label: "Jordan."
    - 1980: Los Angeles Businessmen' Lunch and Other Meetings (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 6)
    - 1980: Fortune 50th Anniversary Symposium (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 7)
    - 1980: U.S.-Soviet Relations Seminar (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 8-9)
    - 1980: Clare Crawford/Reuven Frank (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 10)
    - 1980: Video Weekly (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 11-12)
    - 1980: United Nations Ambassadors Visit (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 13)
    - 1980: Rukeyser/Loeb Party (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 14)
    - 1980: Lubar/Rukeyser Party (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 15)
    - 1980: Fortune Communications Seminar: Monterey (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 16)
    - 1980: People Sales Meeting: Phoenix (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 17)
    - 1980: Time Boston Jubilee Dinner (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 18)
    - 1980: U.S.-West European Relations: Council on Foreign Relations (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 19)
    - 1980: Soviet Issue (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 20)
    - 1980: Election Bet (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 21)
    - 1980: Letters to Republican and Democrat Delegates (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 22)
    - 1980: Heiskell Dinner Toast (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 23)
    - 1980: Heiskell Retirement Dinner (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 24)
    - 1980: J. Walter Thompson Board Dinner (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 25)
    - 1980: Article on China in Washington Star (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 26)
    - 1980: Jessup Book (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 27)
    - 1980: Fortune Departments (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 28)
    - 1980: Ronald Reagan Lunch, Interview and Profile (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 29)
      2 audiocassettes: analog,; 1 15/16 x 1 5/16 in., 1/8 in. tape. On all labels: "Reagan." On envelope: "Reagan campaign speeches 10/82."
    - 1980: Gjon Mili-International Center of Photography Gala (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 30)
    - 1980: Time Life Books Edit Conference (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 31)
    - 1980: Perlez: Daily News Article (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 32)
    - 1980: Think Tanks (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 33)
    - 1980: Revival Foreign Defense Materials (Offsite-box 1030, Folder 34)
    - 1981: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1981: American Renewal (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 1)
    - 1981: Renewal Letters and Articles (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 2)
    - 1981: American "Revival" (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 3-5)
    - 1981: Revival Outlines (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 6)
    - 1981: American Renewal Education (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 7)
    - 1981: Revival "System" Materials (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 8)
    - 1981: Revival Economic Materials (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 9)
    - 1981: Revival Essay Materials (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 10-11)
    - 1981: Remarks at Magazine Staff Meeting: April 23 (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 12)
    - 1981: United Nations Ambassadors Visit (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 13)
      1 audiocassette: analog,; 1 15/16 x 1 5/16 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "UN Dip." On case: "UN Amb file."
    - 1981: DNA Workshop (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 14)
    - 1981: Bonfante Party: 21 Club (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 15)
    - 1981: Council on Foreign Relations Commission on U.S. Policy Toward the Soviet Union (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 16)
    - 1981: Voices of Freedom Conference (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 17)
    - 1981: Loeb/Jaroff/Birnbaum Party (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 18)
    - 1981: Magazine Staff Meeting: June 15 (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 19)
    - 1981: Magazine Group Committee Meeting: 6/24/81 (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 20)
    - 1981: Kiechel's Program Ideas (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 21)
    - 1981: Eileen Einfrank [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1981: Grunwald Employment Agreement [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1981: Jury Duty (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 22)
    - 1981: Media and Society Seminars (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 23)
    - 1981: Time Life Books Staff Meeting: August 10 (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 24)
    - 1981: Washington Star Closing (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 25)
    - 1981: People and Circulation Staff Meeting: September 16 (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 26)
    - 1981: Western 4As Convention (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 27)
    - 1981: Mortimer Adler: Paideia Project 1981 Correspondence (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 28)
    - 1981: Mary Calderone (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 29)
    - 1981: South Africa Ambassador Donald Sole (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 30)
    - 1981: Expense Reports (Offsite-box 1031, Folder 31)
    - 1982: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1982: Time Life Books Visit to Alexandria (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 1-3)
    - 1982: Time Life Books: New Ideas (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 4)
    - 1982: Notes to Archives (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 5)
    - 1982: Remarks to Chicago Staff (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 6)
    - 1982: Otto Count Lambsdorf Intro: Foreign Policy Association Lunch (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 7)
    - 1982: Santa Barbara Symposium [Western Symposium] and Remarks at Time Sales Meeting (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 8)
    - 1982: Housing Conference: Williamsburg, VA (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 9)
    - 1982: Quality (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 10-11)
    - 1982: Walter Bernard's Fortune Redesign (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 12)
    - 1982: Walter Bernard's Fortune Redesign [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1982: Council on Foreign Relations: Discussion Group-North Africa (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 13)
    - 1982: European Business Publishing: Bruce Barnet-Donald Holt (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 14)
    - 1982: George Ball Introduction: Council on Foreign Relations (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 15)
    - 1982: Cap Weinberger Introduction: Foreign Policy Association Lunch (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 16)
    - 1982: Eleanor Graves Party (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 17)
    - 1982: Clare Rosen Farewell Lunch (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 18)
    - 1982: Talk at Pre-board Dinner (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 19)
    - 1982: 4A's [American Association of Advertising Agencies, Inc.] Edit Panel (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 20-21)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: 82151-100 Panels of Time Inc. Editors."
    - 1982: Linda Durham Gallery: Santa Fe (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 22)
      Contains note saying all contents related to the purchase of a painting and were removed to be sent with Grunwald's papers to the Library of Congress.
    - 1982: Victoria and Robert Hughes Dinner (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 23)
    - 1982: Letter and Gift to King Juan Carlos (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 24)
    - 1982: Paul Weaver: Business Lobby (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 25)
    - 1982: Robert Nozick (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 26)
    - 1982: Jerry Kosinski: Village Voice (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 27)
    - 1982: Santa Fe (Offsite-box 1032, Folder 28-29)
      Contains extensive correspondence with pianist Eleanor Steinert.
    - 1982: Together (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 1-2)
    - 1982: Mitchell & Co. Study on Science Magazines (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 3-4)
    - 1982: Silver Rose Reception: Metropolitan Museum of Art (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 5)
    - 1982: Jim Shepley Retirement Toast (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 6)
    - 1982: Fortune International Proposal (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 7)
    - 1982: Tim Foote Retirement Party (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 8)
    - 1982: Tim Foote Memo on Minorities (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 9)
    - 1982: Dr. Karl-Heinz Narjes Intro (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 10)
    - 1982: Chicago Trip (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 11)
    - 1982: Discover Sales Meeting (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 12)
    - 1982: Association of National Advertisers Conference (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 13)
    - 1982: Grunwald Birthday Party: 21 Club (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 14)
    - 1982: Managing Editor at Le Cygne's Wine Cellar (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 15)
    - 1982: Washington Week: John Morton (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 16)
    - 1982: Expense Reports (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 17)
    - 1982: Electronic Publishing Briefing (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 18-19)
    - 1982: TV-Cable Week Presentation (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 20)
    - 1982: Additions to TV-Cable Week Financial Package (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 21)
    - 1982: TV-Cable Week COO Review Summary (Offsite-box 1033, Folder 22-23)
    - 1982: TV-Cable Week Financial Plans (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 1)
    - 1982: TV-Cable Week Cost Analysis (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 2)
    - 1982: Cable Magazine (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 3)
    - 1982: Fortune Conference (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 4)
    - 1982: Time Inc. Western Symposium [Santa Barbara Symposium] (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 5-7)
      Time Inc. hosted a symposium with panels titled "The Risk Merchants of Silicon Valley," "Computers and Information," "The New Immigrants," and "Terrorism." Panelists included James Treybig of Tandem Computers, Steve Jobs of Apple Computer, and Utah Governor Scott Matheson. Guests included California Governor Edmund "Jerry" Brown. Materials include the symposium agenda and presentation transcripts.
    - 1982: Together: Door-to-Door Survey (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 8)
    - 1982: Quality: Study of Potential Readers (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 9)
    - 1983: Committee for Free World Conference (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 10)
    - 1983: Trip to Los Angeles (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 11)
    - 1983: Walter Guzzardi: Princeton Seminar (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 12)
    - 1983: Time Inc. / SIPI Dinner for Dr. Lewis Thomas (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 13)
    - 1983: Boston Ad Sales Lunch (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 14)
    - 1983: Expense Reports (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 15)
    - 1983: Editors Panel: Food Marketing Institute: Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 16)
    - 1983: Ralph Graves Dinner: Cote Basque (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 17)
    - 1983: Users Evaluation of Teletext Study (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 18)
    - 1983: Executive Compensation Strategy (Offsite-box 1034, Folder 19)
    - 1983: TV-Cable Week (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 1-3)
    - 1983: Questions for Andropov Interview (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 4)
    - 1983: Clark Schiller Reports (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 5)
      Includes study regarding public awareness of magazines.
    - 1983: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1983: Minutes of Tuesday Group Meetings (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 6)
      The Tuesday Group consists of various Time Inc. executives.
    - 1983: Time Cover Show: Paris (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 7)
    - 1983: Authority Project (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 8)
    - 1983: Mitterand Interview (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 9)
    - 1983: Margaret Thatcher Interview (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 10)
    - 1983: Fortune Test (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 11)
    - 1983: Communications Essay: 1982 Annual Report (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 12)
    - 1983: Quality (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 13)
    - 1983: Together (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 14-15)
    - 1983: Magazine Development: General (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 16)
    - 1983: Thayer Bigelow Memos on Strategic Planning (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 17)
    - 1983: Time 60th Anniversary (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 18-19)
    - 1983: The Rogosin Institute (Offsite-box 1035, Folder 20)